Vanja Paunovic

Software Engineer

Belgrade, Serbia (+381) 65 541 9360 vana997@gmail.com in linkedin.com/in/vpaunovic q github.com/dzimiks

Summary

I am a passionate, self-motivated and committed computer science student. The majority of my spare time I've spent on learning new algorithms and data structures. I like to improve my skills and knowledge while working on interested projects. I have worked and thrived in a team setting through the internships I have had in the last two years. Learning from my teammates and constantly interacting with clients taught me discipline and it's giving me motivation to progress.

Work History

Startup

July, 2017 - September, 2017

Full Stack Engineer

Developed MEAN stack web applications.

Created administrator management system for on-site content upload.

Designed and implemented web pages.

Devana Technologies

July, 2016 - September, 2016

Devana Technologies

Frontend Developer Internship Worked in small and efficient team.

Education

Bachelor in Computer Science Union University, Faculty of Computing

2016 - present

High School Diploma

2012 - 2016

XIV Belgrade Gymnasium

Projects

GeKoSeM - Generic document manager. It can be used for organizing and editing documents with textual or graphical editor.

Universal Installer - Universal Installer is app that simulates installation process. It was a college project for Software Design course.

TetrisAI - TetrisAI represents basic Tetris simulation. It was my seminary project for Intelligent systems course.

PanRock Global - Designed complete website and implemented many functionalities.

FEFA - Maintained website and implemented news feed.

Courses

WP Academy 2017

March, 2017 - April, 2017

WordPress Community Serbia

Selected from 180 applicants. Worked on theme development and online shops using WooCommerce.

Languages

English - Professional working proficiency

Serbian - Native or bilingual proficiency

German - Elementary proficiency (Deutsches Sprachdiplom der Kultusministerkonferenz - A2)

Skills

Java

C/C++

_ ...

Python

HTML 5

000

CSS 3

Javascript